Black Sparrow Press Collection, 1966-1994 (bulk 1973-1993)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Book Files, 1973-1993
  - #429 Heavy Daughters Blues, Coleman, Wanda, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - #429 Heavy Daughters Blues, Coleman, Wanda, Artwork, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - #429 Heavy Daughters Blues, Coleman, Wanda, First Manuscript, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - #429 Heavy Daughters Blues, Coleman, Wanda, Revised Manuscript, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - #429 Heavy Daughters Blues, Coleman, Wanda, First Proof, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - #429 Heavy Daughters Blues,Coleman, Wanda, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - #430 Movie: Barfly, Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - #430 Movie: Barfly, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - #430 Movie: Barfly, Bukowski,Charles, Photographs, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - #430 Movie: Barfly, Bukowski,Charles, Photographs by Michael Montfort, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - #430 Movie: Barfly, Bukowski,Charles, Manuscript, Discarded Materials, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - #430 Movie: Barfly, Bukowski, Charles, Miscellaneous Texts, Discarded Materials, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - #430 Movie: Barfly, Bukowski,Charles, Edited Screenplay, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - #430 Movie: Barfly, Bukowski,Charles, Screenplay Manuscript, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - #430 Movie: Barfly, Bukowski,Charles, First Proof, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 8, Folder 9)
  - #430 Movie: Movie: Barfly,Bukowski, Charles, Second Proofs, 1987 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - #430 Movie: Movie: Barfly,Bukowski, Charles,3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - #431 Memoir of Maurice Magnus, Lawrence, D.H., Correspondence, 1987 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - #431 Memoir of Maurice Magnus, Lawrence, D.H., Artwork, Notes, 1987 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - #431 Memoir of Maurice Magnus, Lawrence, D.H., Manuscript, 1987 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - #431 Memoir of Maurice Magnus, Lawrence, D.H., First Proof, 1987 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - #431 Memoir of Maurice Magnus, Lawrence, D.H., Second Proof, 1987 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - #431 Memoir of Maurice Magnus, Lawrence, D.H., 3 Hardcover copies, 1987 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - #432 A Very Good Land To Fall With, Volume 3, Sanford, John, Correspondence, Artwork, 1987 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - #432 A Very Good Land To Fall With, Volume 3, Sanford, John, Manuscript (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - #432 A Very Good Land To Fall With, Volume 3, Sanford, John, Manuscript (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - #432 A Very Good Land To Fall With, Volume 3, Sanford, John, Manuscript (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - #432 A Very Good Land To Fall With, Volume 3, Sanford, John, First Proof, 1987 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - #432 A Very Good Land To Fall With, Volume 3, Sanford, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - #433 Full of Life, Fante, John, Correspondence, Artwork, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - #433 Full of Life, Fante, John, Manuscript, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - #433 Full of Life, Fante, John, First Proof, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - #433 Full of Life, Fante, John, Second Proof, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - #433 Full of Life, Fante, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - #434 Faces Reappear, Jaffe, Sherril, Correspondence, Artwork, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - #434 Faces Reappear, Jaffe, Sherril, Manuscript, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - #434 Faces Reappear, Jaffe, Sherril, First Proof, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - #434 Faces Reappear, Jaffe, Sherril, Second Proof, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - #434 Faces Reappear, Jaffe, Sherril, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - #435 Essays: Personal and Impersonal, Hindus, Milton, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - #435 Essays: Personal and Impersonal, Hindus, Milton, Manuscript, 1988 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - #435 Essays: Personal and Impersonal, Hindus, Milton, Second Proof, 1988 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - #435 Essays: Personal and Impersonal, Hindus, Milton, 2 Hardcover copies, 1988 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - #436 The Movie Critics, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Manuscript, 2 Hardcover copies, 5 Softcover copy, 1 Unbound copy, 1988 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - #436 Brotherhood of the Grape, Fante, John, Artwork, 1988 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - #436 Brotherhood of the Grape, Fante, John, Manuscript, 1988 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - #436 Brotherhood of the Grape, Fante, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1988 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - #438 Roominghouse,, Bukowski, Charles, Doodles, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - #438 Roominghouse,, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - #438 Roominghouse,, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - #438 Roominghouse,, Bukowski, Charles, Original Poems Manuscript Selected, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - #438 Roominghouse,, Bukowski, Charles, Rejected Poems Manuscript, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - #438 Roominghouse,, Bukowski, Charles, First proof - office copy, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - #438 Roominghouse,, Bukowski, Charles, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - #439 Bukowski at Bellevue, Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - #439 Bukowski at Bellevue, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1988 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - #439 Bukowski at Bellevue, Bukowski, Charles, 3 VHS 1-hr video recordings of Bukowski at Bellevue Community College (2 sealed, 1 open), 1988 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - #440 Desire, Bromige, David, Artwork, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - #440 Desire, Bromige, David, Manuscript, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - #440 Desire, Bromige, David, Revised Manuscript, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - #440 Desire, Bromige, David, Western States Book Awards, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - #440 Desire, Bromige, David, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1 uncorrected proof, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - #441 A War Of Eyes And Other Stories, Coleman, Wanda, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - #441 A War Of Eyes And Other Stories, Coleman, Wanda, Artwork, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - #441 A War Of Eyes And Other Stories, Coleman, Wanda, First Manuscript, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - #441 A War Of Eyes And Other Stories, Coleman, Wanda, Western States Book Awards, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - #441 A War Of Eyes And Other Stories, Coleman, Wanda, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1 uncorrected proof, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - #442 Will She Understand? Dawson, Fielding, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - #442 Will She Understand? Dawson, Fielding, Artwork, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - #442 Will She Understand? Dawson, Fielding, Discarded Materials, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - #442 Will She Understand? Dawson, Fielding, Manuscript, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - #442 Will She Understand? Dawson, Fielding, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - #443 Cultural Affairs In Boston, Wieners, John, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - #443 Cultural Affairs In Boston, Wieners, John, Artwork, 1988 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - #443 Cultural Affairs In Boston, Wieners, John, Discarded Materials, 1988 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - #443 Cultural Affairs In Boston, Wieners, John, Manuscript, 1988 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - #443 Cultural Affairs In Boston, Wieners, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1988 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - #444 Emerald Ice, Wakoski, Diane, Correspondence and Artwork, 1988 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - #444 Emerald Ice, Wakoski, Diane, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - #444 Emerald Ice, Wakoski, Diane, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - #444 Emerald Ice, Wakoski, Diane, First proofs (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - #444 Emerald Ice, Wakoski, Diane, First proofs (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - #444 Emerald Ice, Wakoski, Diane, 1 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1988 (Box 205)
  - #444 Emerald Ice,Wakoski, Diane, 2 Hardcover copies, 1988 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - #445 In The Zone, Chester, Laura, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - #445 In The Zone, Chester, Laura, Artwork, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - #445 In The Zone, Chester, Laura, Manuscript, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - #445 In The Zone, Chester, Laura, First Proof, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - #446 If You Let Them Kill You, They Will, Bukowski, Charles, New Year's Greeting Artwork, Tip-Ins (12), and Manuscript, 1989 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - #446 If You Let Them Kill You, They Will, Bukowski, Charles, 2 Hardcover copies, 4 Softcover, 1989 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - #447 A Nation of Nothing but Poetry, Olson, Charles, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - #447 A Nation of Nothing but Poetry,Olson, Charles, Artwork, 1989 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - #447 A Nation of Nothing but Poetry,Olson, Charles, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - #447 A Nation of Nothing but Poetry,Olson, Charles, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - #447 A Nation of Nothing but Poetry,Olson, Charles, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1989 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - #448 The Art of Being Ruled, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - #448 The Art of Being Ruled, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, 1989 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - #448 The Art of Being Ruled, Lewis, Wyndham, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - #448 The Art of Being Ruled, Lewis, Wyndham, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - #448 The Art of Being Ruled, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1989 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - #448 The Art of Being Ruled, Lewis, Wyndham, 2 Hardcover copies, 1989 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1989 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, First run out (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, First run out (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, First proofs (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, First proofs (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscripts (1of 2), 1989 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscripts (2 of 2), Cover Art Slides - see Oversized Materials, 1989 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, Cover Art Slides; See Oversized Items, Box 298, 1989 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - #450 A Walk in The Fire, Sanford, John, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - #450 A Walk in The Fire, Sanford, John, Artwork, 1989 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - #450 A Walk in The Fire, Sanford, John, Manuscript (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - #450 A Walk in The Fire, Sanford, John, Manuscript, Manuscript (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 213, Folder 4, Folder 5)
  - #450 A Walk in The Fire, Sanford, John, Manuscript (3 of 3) (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - #450 A Walk in The Fire, Sanford, John, Manuscript, 1 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - #450 A Walk in The Fire,Sanford, John, 2 Hardcover copies, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - #451 Hotel Cro-Magnon,Eshleman, Clayton, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - #451 Hotel Cro-Magnon, Eshleman, Clayton, Artwork, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - #451 Hotel Cro-Magnon, Eshleman, Clayton, Manuscript, 1989 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - #451 Hotel Cro-Magnon, Eshleman, Clayton, Artwork, Discarded Materials (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - #451 Hotel Cro-Magnon, Eshleman, Clayton, Discarded Materials (2 of 2)., 1989 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - #451 Hotel Cro-Magnon, Eshleman, Clayton, First proof, First proof; 1989 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - #451 Hotel Cro-Magnon, Eshleman, Clayton, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1989 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - #452 Objects Of Reverie, Callis, Jo Ann, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - #452 Objects Of Reverie, Callis, Jo Ann, Artwork, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - #452 Objects Of Reverie, Callis, Jo Ann, Manuscript and Slides, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - #452 Objects Of Reverie, Callis, Jo Ann, First proof and Second Proof, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - #452 Objects Of Reverie, Callis, Jo Ann, First proof and Second Proof, 1 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - #453 A Personal Correspondence,Fante, John, and Mencken, H.L., Correspondence, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - #453 A Personal Correspondence, Fante, John, and Mencken, H.L., Copies of letters from J. Fante, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - #453 A Personal Correspondence, Fante, John, and Mencken, H.L., Artwork, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - #453 A Personal Correspondence, Fante, John, and Mencken, H.L., Manuscript, 1989 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - #453 A Personal Correspondence, Fante, John, and Mencken, H.L., First Proof, 1989 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - #453 A Personal Correspondence, Fante, John, and Mencken, H.L., Second Proof, 1989 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - #453 A Personal Correspondence, Fante, John, and Mencken, H.L., 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1989 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - #454 The Complete Poems, Reznikoff, Charles, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - #454 The Complete Poems, Reznikoff, Charles, Artwork, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - #454 The Complete Poems, Reznikoff, Charles, Text revisions, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - #454 The Complete Poems, Reznikoff, Charles, 3 Softcover copies of The Complete Poems, Vol I and II (Text revisions), 1989 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - #455 Creatures of Habit and Creatures of Change, Wyndham, Lewis, Editor's synopsis, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - #455 Creatures of Habit and Creatures of Change, Wyndham, Lewis, Artwork, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - #455 Creatures of Habit and Creatures of Change, Wyndham, Lewis, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - #455 Creatures of Habit and Creatures of Change, Wyndham, Lewis, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - #455 Creatures of Habit and Creatures of Change, Wyndham, Lewis, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - #456 Radiant Silhouette, Yau, John, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - #456 Radiant Silhouette, Yau, John, Artwork, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - #456 Radiant Silhouette, Yau, John, Magazine Appearances, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - #456 Radiant Silhouette, Yau, John, Catalogue Essays, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - #456 Radiant Silhouette, Yau, John, First Draft, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - #456 Radiant Silhouette, Yau, John, Discarded Materials, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - #456 Radiant Silhouette, Yau, John, Manuscript, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - #456 Radiant Silhouette, Yau, John, First Proof, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - #456 Radiant Silhouette, Yau, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1989 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - #457 The Stone Baby, Chester, Laura, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - #457 The Stone Baby, Chester, Laura, Artwork, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - #457 The Stone Baby, Chester, Laura, Discarded Materials, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - #457 The Stone Baby, Chester, Laura, First Draft, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - #457 The Stone Baby, Chester, Laura, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - #457 The Stone Baby, Chester, Laura, Manuscript, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - #457 The Stone Baby, Chester, Laura, First Proof, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - #457 The Stone Baby ,Chester, Laura, 3 Hardcover copies, 2 Softcovers, 1989 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - #458 Scars Make Your Body More Interesting, Jaffe, Sherril, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - #458 Scars Make Your Body More Interesting, Jaffe, Sherril, Artwork, 1989 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - #458 Scars Make Your Body More Interesting, Jaffe, Sherril, Manuscript, 1989 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - #458 Scars Make Your Body More Interesting, Jaffe, Sherril, Second proof, 1989 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - #458 Scars Make Your Body More Interesting, Jaffe, Sherril, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1989 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - #459 We Ain't Got No Money, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - #459 We Ain't Got No Money, Bukowski, Charles, Second Proofs, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - #459 We Ain't Got No Money, Bukowski, Charles, Book copies: 2 Hardcover, 3 Softcovers, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - #460 Tarr: The 1918 Version, Wyndham, Lewis, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - #460 Tarr: The 1918 Version, Wyndham, Lewis, Artwork, 1990 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - #460 Tarr: The 1918 Version, Wyndham, Lewis, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - #460 Tarr: The 1918 Version, Wyndham, Lewis, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - #460 Tarr: The 1918 Version, Wyndham, Lewis, First Proof (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - #460 Tarr: The 1918 Version, Wyndham, Lewis, First Proof (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - #460 Tarr: The 1918 Version, Wyndham, Lewis, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - #461 Fractured Karma,, Clark, Tom, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - #461 Fractured Karma,, Clark, Tom, Artwork, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - #461 Fractured Karma,, Clark, Tom, Discarded Materials, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - #461 Fractured Karma,, Clark, Tom, Manuscript, 1990 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - #461 Fractured Karma,, Clark, Tom, First Proof (Tom), 1990 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - #461 Fractured Karma,, Clark, Tom, First Proof (Seamus), 1990 (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - #461 Fractured Karma,, Clark, Tom, Second Proof, 1990 (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - #461 Fractured Karma,Clark, Tom, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1990 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - #462 Comics, Crumb, R., Artwork; See Oversized Items, Box 298, 1990 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - #462 Comics, Crumb, R., Artwork; See Oversized Items, Box 298, 1990 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - #463 Septuagenarian Stew,Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence, Artwork; See Oversized Items, Box 298, 1990 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - #463 Septuagenarian Stew, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - #463 Septuagenarian Stew, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - #463 Septuagenarian Stew, Bukowski, Charles, First proof (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - #463 Septuagenarian Stew, Bukowski, Charles, First proof (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - #463 Septuagenarian Stew, Bukowski, Charles, 1 Hardcover copy (in shrink-wrap), 1 Softcover copy, 1990 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - #463 Septuagenarian Stew, Bukowski, Charles, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover copy, 1990 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - #464 Correspondence, VOL 9., Olson, C. and Creeley, R., Correspondence, 1990 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - #464 Correspondence, VOL 9., Olson, C. and Creeley, R., Artwork, 1990 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - #464 Correspondence, VOL 9., Olson, C. and Creeley, R., Manuscripts (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - #464 Correspondence, VOL 9., Olson, C. and Creeley, R., Manuscripts (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - #464 Correspondence, VOL 9., Olson, C. and Creeley, R., Second proofs (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - #464 Correspondence, VOL 9., Olson, C. and Creeley, R., Second proofs (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - #464 Correspondence, VOL 9., Olson, C. and Creeley, R., Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover copy, 1990 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - #465 Abhorrence’s, Dorn, Edward, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - #465 Abhorrence’s, Dorn, Edward, Artwork, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - #465 Abhorrence’s, Dorn, Edward, Manuscripts, 1990 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - #465 Abhorrence’s, Dorn, Edward, Discarded Materials, 1990 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - #465 Abhorrence’s, Dorn, Edward, Second proofs, 1990 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - #465 Abhorrence’s, Dorn, Edward, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1990 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - #466 Head of A Sad Angel, Chester, Alfred, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - #466 Head of A Sad Angel, Chester, Alfred, Artwork, 1990 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - #466 Head of A Sad Angel, Chester, Alfred, Book of Stories, 1990 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - #466 Head of A Sad Angel, Chester, Alfred, Manuscript, 1990 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - #466 Head of A Sad Angel, Chester, Alfred, Second Proofs (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - #466 Head of A Sad Angel, Chester, Alfred, Second Proofs (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - #466 Head of A Sad Angel, Chester, Alfred, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1990 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - #467 Men, Women and Vehicles, Bromige, David, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - #467 Men, Women and Vehicles, Bromige, David, Artwork, 1990 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - #467 Men, Women and Vehicles, Bromige, David, Manuscript, 1990 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - #467 Men, Women and Vehicles, Bromige, David, Discarded Materials (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - #467 Men, Women and Vehicles, Bromige, David, Discarded Materials (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - #467 Men, Women and Vehicles, Bromige, David, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1990 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - #468 The Engendering Flood, Everson, David, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - #468 The Engendering Flood, Everson, David, Artwork, 1990 (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - #468 The Engendering Flood, Everson, David, Manuscript, 1990 (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - #468 The Engendering Flood, Everson, David, First proof, 1990 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - #468 The Engendering Flood, Everson, David, Second proof, 1990 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - #468 The Engendering Flood, Everson, David, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1990 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - #469 African Sleeping Sickness, Coleman, Wanda, Artwork, 1990 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - #469 African Sleeping Sickness, Coleman, Wanda, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - #469 African Sleeping Sickness, Coleman, Wanda, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - #469 African Sleeping Sickness, Coleman, Wanda, First Revisions, 1990 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - #469 African Sleeping Sickness, Coleman, Wanda, First Proof (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - #469 African Sleeping Sickness, Coleman, Wanda, First Proof (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - #469 African Sleeping Sickness, Coleman, Wanda, 3 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1990 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - #470 Home Sick, Berlin, Lucia, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - #470 Home Sick, Berlin, Lucia, Artwork, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - #470 Home Sick, Berlin, Lucia, Artwork, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - #470 Home Sick, Berlin, Lucia, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - #470 Home Sick, Berlin, Lucia, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - #470 Home Sick, Berlin, Lucia, Discarded Materials, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - #470 Home Sick, Berlin, Lucia, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - #471 Prologue "Ask The Dust.” Fante, John, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - #471 Prologue "Ask The Dust", Fante, John, Artwork, 1990 (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - #471 Prologue "Ask The Dust", Fante, John, Manuscript, 1990 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - #471 Prologue "Ask The Dust", Fante, John, 2 Softcover copies, 1990 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - #472 Medea, The Sorceress, Wakoski, Diane, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - #472 Medea, The Sorceress, Wakoski, Diane, Artwork, 1991 (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - #472 Medea, The Sorceress, Wakoski, Diane, Manuscript, 1991 (Box 240, Folder 7)
  - #472 Medea, The Sorceress, Wakoski, Diane, First proof, 1991 (Box 240, Folder 8)
  - #472 Medea, The Sorceress, Wakoski, Diane, 1 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 240, Folder 9)
  - #472 Medea, The Sorceress, Wakoski, Diane, 2 Hardcover copies, 1991 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - #473 In The Morning, and at Night and in Between, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Manuscript, and Back Matter, 1991 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - #473 In The Morning, and at Night and in Between, Bukowski, Charles, 1 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover copy, 1991 (Box 241, Folder 3)